do you mind if I smoke it won't affect
the test all right I'm gonna ask you a
series of questions just relax and
answer them as simply as you can it's
your birthday someone gives you a
calfskin wallet I wouldn't accept it
also I'd report the person who gave it
to me to the police you've got a little
boy he shows you his Butterfly
Collection plus the killing jar I take
him to the doctor
you're watching television suddenly
realized there's a wasp crawling on your
arm I'd kill it you're reading a
magazine you come across a full-page
nude photo of a girl is this testing
whether I'm a replicant or a lesbian mr.
Deckard just answer the questions please
you show it to your husband he likes it
so much he hangs it on your bedroom wall
I should be in there for him you're
watching a stage play a banquet is in
progress the guests are enjoying an
appetizer of raw oysters yon strengthen
system oiled dog
would you step out for a few moments
Rachael
thank you she's a replicant isn't she
I'm impressed how many questions does it
usually take to spot I don't get it
Tyrone how many questions 20 30
cross-referenced it took more than 100
for Rachael didn't it she doesn't know
she's beginning to suspect I think you
suspect how can it not know what it is
commerce is our goal here at Tyrell more
human than human is our motto
Rachael is an experiment nothing more we
began to recognize in them strange
obsession after all they are emotionally
and experienced with only a few years in
which to store up the experiences which
you and I take for granted if we get
them past we create a cushion or pillow
for their emotions and consequently we
can control them better memories you're
talking about memories
[Music]